Jaime Rocafull Valero

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

jaimek89@gmail.com 07727 147277 linkedin.com/in/jaime-rocafull-valero-529b89142 London, United Kingdom

Profile

Experienced in the mechanical engineering field, in the sector of industrial refrigeration and air conditioning. I have recently discovered the world of web development, which has deeply stirred my interest and curiosity. After attending a Bootcamp in Barcelona, Spain, I have discovered a passion for design and development.

Education

Full Stack Developer

Skylab Coders Academy 2018 - 2018

Mechanical Engineer's degree

Florida Universitaria 2013 - 2014

Diploma of Higher Education in Mechanical Engineering

Florida Universitaria 2008 - 2012

Languages

Catalan Native or bilingual

English Professional working

Italian Elementary

Spanish Native or bilingual

Experience

Mechanical Engineer Tefri Valencia SL Mar 2017 - Nov 2018 Valencia, Spain

Food And Beverage Attendant Hilton London Metropole

Feb 2016 - Mar 2017 London, United Kingdom

Mechanical Engineer & Operations Manager Montajes frigoricos J.R. S.L.

Dec 2013 - Aug 2015 Valencia, Spain

Mechanical Engineer Montajes Frigorícos J.R. S.L.

Aug 2012 - Dec 2013 Valencia, Spain

Internship PECOMARK

Aug 2011 - Sep 2011 Valencia Area, Spain

Internship Diseños Aysa S.L.

Jun 2010 - Oct 2010 Valencia Area, Spain

Skills

React.js, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Agile Methodologies, Engineering, TDD, Node.js, Git, HTML5, jQuery, MongoDB, Github, SASS, JSON, AJAX, AutoCAD, REST, Express.js, Jasmine Framework, ES6, Markdown Optimization, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), Mocha, Parcel